Guide to the Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
- Administrative Records, 1937-2002; 1937 2002; 98.25 linear feet
  - Prominent Members
    - Blair, Peter D.
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Sarewitz, Daniel, undated (Box 1.05, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Sauer, Petr, 1997 (Box 1.05, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Scadden, Lawrence A., 1997 (Box 1.05, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Schaffer, Daniel, 1996 (Box 1.05, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Schuler, Richard, 1996 (Box 1.05, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Seltzer, Raymond, 1997 (Box 1.05, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Shaffer, Gary, 1997 (Box 1.05, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Shaw, Robert W., 1998 (Box 1.05, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Shimberg, Steven, 1998 (Box 1.05, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Shimp, Robert, 1997 (Box 1.05, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Shuler, Richard, 1998 (Box 1.05, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Simon, Gary D., 1996-1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Sink, Claire H., 1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Smith, Charles, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Smith, Michael, 1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Smith, Philip M., 1996-1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Snyder, Michael G., 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Snyderman, Ralph, 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Sohl, Jeffery, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Stallworth, Cedric, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Stevens, Candice, undated (Box 1.051, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Stiles, Skip, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Stimpson, Catharine R., 1996-1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Stine, Deborah, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Stoy, Roger W., 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Suskin, Mark A., 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: T, 1996-1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Tassey, Gregory, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Taylor, Max F. J. R., 1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Teich, Albert H., 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Templin, Robert, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Thompson, William J., 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Tittle, David, 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Tornatzky, Louis G., 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Treppe, Frank, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Tsybin, Alexander S., 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Tulloh, Charles A., 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: U, 1996-1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: V, 1996-1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Valentino, F. William, 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Varley, Andrew P., 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: W, 1996-1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Ward, Thomas G., 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Watson, Robert F., 1996-1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Weimer, Tom, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: West, Guy R., 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Wetstone, Greg, 1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: White, Irvin L., 1996-1999 (Box 1.051, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: White, Robert, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Whyte, Anne, 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Wiener, Jonathan, 1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Williamson, Samuel J., 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Wince-Smith, Deborah, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Winship, Lawrence J., 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: Woodard, Joan B., 1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, Individuals: X-Z, 1997-1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1996-1998 (Box 1.051, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Armed Forces Communication and Electronics Association, 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Association for International Agriculture and Rural Development, 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Alabama, University of - Huntsville, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 49)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: American Chemical Society, 1997 (Box 1.051, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: American Electro Science Foundation, 1996 (Box 1.051, Folder 51)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: American Nuclear Society, 1996 (Box 1.052, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Annual Reviews, Inc., 1997 (Box 1.052, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Apple Computer Inc., 1996 (Box 1.052, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: American Physical Society, 1996 (Box 1.052, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Army, Department of, 1996 (Box 1.052, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: American Society of Mechanical Engineers International, 1998 (Box 1.052, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Association for Women In Science, 1996 (Box 1.052, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Battelle Memorial Institute, 1995-1998 (Box 1.052, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Betchart Expeditions, 1997-1998 (Box 1.052, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Brattle Group, The, 1996 (Box 1.052, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: California, University of - Berkeley, 1997 (Box 1.052, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Canadian Energy Research Institute (Box 1.052, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Career Fair Coordinators, 1997 (Box 1.052, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1996 (Box 1.052, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Carnegie Mellon University, 1996 (Box 1.052, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Cary Travel, 1996-1997 (Box 1.052, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Chicago Area Sigma Xi Chapters, 1997 (Box 1.052, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Council of Engineering and Scientific Society Executives, 1996-1998 (Box 1.052, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Council of Engineering and Scientific Society Executives, 1996-1998 (Box 1.052, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Chemical Industry Institute of Toxicology, 1997 (Box 1.053, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Cosmos Club, 1998 (Box 1.053, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Council on Foreign Relations Study Group, 1996-1997 (Box 1.053, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Covance Biotechnology Services Inc., 1997 (Box 1.053, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Commission on Professionals in Science and Technology, 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: D, 1997-1998 (Box 1.053, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Decision Focus Inc., 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Defense Intelligence Agency, 1993 (Box 1.053, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Diagnostic Instrumentation and Analysis Laboratory, 1998 (Box 1.053, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: E, 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Energy and Natural Resources, Committee On, 1997 (Box 1.053, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Energy Foundation, 1999 (Box 1.053, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Energy Modeling Forum, 1997 (Box 1.053, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Environmental and Energy Study Institute, 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Environmental Protection Agency, Science Advisory Board, 1997 (Box 1.053, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Federation of American Scientists, 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Federation of Materials Societies, 1998 (Box 1.053, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: First Union National Bank of North Carolina, 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Flippin, Bruce and Porter, 1997 (Box 1.053, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Gas Research Institute, 1997 (Box 1.053, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Government-University-Industry Research Roundtable, 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: H, 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Heineman Medical Research Inc., 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Houston Advanced Research Center, 1998 (Box 1.053, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Hydrogen and Fuel Cell Letter, 1996 (Box 1.053, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: International Association for Technology Assessment and Forecasting Institutions, 1996-1998 (Box 1.053, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Institute of Global Competitiveness, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Institute for Operations Research and the Management Sciences, 1997 (Box 1.054, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: International Higher Education Academy of Sciences, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: International Research Center for Energy and Economic Development, 1995-1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Italian Trade Commission, Government Agency, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: KOZ, 1997-1999 (Box 1.054, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, Energy Advisory Committee, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Loka Institute, The, 1997 (Box 1.054, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Midwest Research Institute, 1997-1998 (Box 1.054, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: National Coalition for Research and Development, 1997 (Box 1.054, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: National Committee on Retirement Policy, 1998 (Box 1.054, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: O'Brien Atkins, 1997 (Box 1.054, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Queensland, University of, 1997 (Box 1.054, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Science and Technology in Congress, 1997 (Box 1.054, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Structural Engineers Association of Illinois, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Semiconductor Research Corporation, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: SRI International, undated (Box 1.054, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Swarthmore College, 1998 (Box 1.054, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Technical Education Research Centers, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Texas A & M University, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: TMP Video Communications, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: Tropical Studies, Organization For, 1996 (Box 1.054, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: United States Association for Energy Economics, 1998 (Box 1.054, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, Institutions: W, 1996-1997 (Box 1.054, Folder 24)
      - Diversity Committee, 1998 (Box 1.054, Folder 25)
      - Duties of Sigma Xi President, undated (Box 1.054, Folder 26)
      - Education Advisory Panel, 1999 (Box 1.054, Folder 27)
      - Education Workshop, 1998 (Box 1.054, Folder 28)
      - Education Workshop, 1998 (Box 1.054, Folder 29)
      - Ethical Challenges and Practical Solutions for Managers in Research Workshop, 10 Sep. 1999 (Box 1.055, Folder 1)
      - Ethical Challenges and Practical Solutions Workshop/2000 Forum Planning Conference, 10-11 Sep. 1999 (Box 1.055, Folder 2)
      - Ethics, 1998 (Box 1.055, Folder 3)
      - Ethics Advisory Committee, 2000 (Box 1.055, Folder 4)
      - Ethics Article, 19 Sep. 1999 (Box 1.19, Folder 8)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 18 Jul. 1996 (Box 1.055, Folder 5)
      - Executive Committee Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting, 6 Mar. 1997 (Box 1.055, Folder 6)
      - Executive Committee Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting, 6 Mar. 1997 (Box 1.055, Folder 7)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 29-30 May 1997 (Box 1.055, Folder 8)
      - Executive Committee Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting, 19 Nov. 1997 (Box 1.055, Folder 9)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 16 Jan. 1998 (Box 1.055, Folder 10)
      - Executive Committee Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting, 15 Jun. 1998 (Box 1.056, Folder 1)
      - Executive Committee Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting, 11 Nov. 1998 (Box 1.056, Folder 2)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 1999 (Box 1.056, Folder 3)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 19 Mar. 1999 (Box 1.056, Folder 4)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, Nov. 1999 (Box 1.056, Folder 5)
      - Executive Committee Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting, 3 Nov. 1999 (Box 1.056, Folder 6)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 15 Apr. 2000 (Box 1.056, Folder 7)
      - Executive Committee Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting, 8 Nov. 2000 (Box 1.056, Folder 8)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 25 May 2001 (Box 1.056, Folder 9)
      - Expense Reports, 1996 (Box 1.057, Folder 1)
      - Expense Reports, 1997 (Box 1.057, Folder 2)
      - Expense Reports, 1998 (Box 1.057, Folder 3)
      - Expense Reports, 1999 (Box 1.057, Folder 4)
      - Expense Reports, 2000 (Box 1.057, Folder 5)
      - Expense Reports, 2001 (Box 1.057, Folder 6)
      - Finances, 1998 (Box 1.057, Folder 7)
      - Forum and Annual Meeting, Executive Committee Meeting, Board of Directors Meeting, 6 & 10 Mar. 1996 (Box 1.058, Folder 1)
      - Forum and Annual Meeting, Executive Committee Meeting, Board of Directors Meeting, 6 & 10 Mar. 1996 (Box 1.058, Folder 2)
      - Forum, 1997 (Box 1.058, Folder 3)
      - Forum Planning: Education: National Science Foundation, 1997 (Box 1.058, Folder 4)
      - Forum & Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 1.058, Folder 5)
      - Forum and Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 1.058, Folder 6)
      - Forum, 1997 (Box 1.059, Folder 1)
      - Forum: Funding, 1999 (Box 1.059, Folder 2)
      - Forum Planning: Education, 1999 (Box 1.059, Folder 3)
      - Forum Planning: Education, 1999 (Box 1.059, Folder 4)
      - Forum Planning: Education, 1999 (Box 1.059, Folder 6)
      - Forum Planning: Education, 1999 (Box 1.059, Folder 7)
      - Forum Planning: Education, 1999 (Box 1.06, Folder 1)
      - Forum Planning: Education, 1999 (Box 1.06, Folder 2)
      - Forum Planning: Education: Project Kaleidoscope, 1999 (Box 1.06, Folder 3)
      - Forum Planning: Ethics, 1999-2000 (Box 1.06, Folder 4)
      - Forum Planning: Ethics, 1999-2000 (Box 1.06, Folder 5)
      - Forum Planning: Ethics, 1999-2000 (Box 1.06, Folder 6)
      - Forum Welcome, 1999 (Box 1.06, Folder 7)
      - Forum Planning: Ethics, 2000 (Box 1.06, Folder 8)
      - Forum Planning: Ethics, 2000 (Box 1.061, Folder 1)
      - Forum Planning: Ethics, 2000 (Box 1.061, Folder 2)
      - Forum and Annual Meeting Staff Manual, 9-10 Nov. 2000 (Box 1.061, Folder 3)
      - Forum and Annual Meeting Staff Manual, 9-10 Nov. 2000 (Box 1.061, Folder 4)
      - Germany Trip, Sep. 2000 (Box 1.061, Folder 5)
      - Holt Introduction, undated (Box 1.061, Folder 6)
      - Insurance, 1997 (Box 1.061, Folder 7)
      - International Committee, 1998 (Box 1.061, Folder 8)
      - Forum Planning: Education, 1999 (Box 1.059, Folder 5)
      - Introduction for Assembly, 1997 (Box 1.061, Folder 9)
      - K-12 Workshop, 1999 (Box 1.061, Folder 10)
      - Media Resource Service, 1996-1998 (Box 1.061, Folder 11)
      - Media Resource Service, 1996-1998 (Box 1.061, Folder 12)
      - Meeting: American Association for the Advancement of Science Colloquium: Science and Technology Policy, 17-19 Apr. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 1)
      - Meeting: Conference Call: Wiley, Robbins, Bugliarello regarding draft, 23 Apr. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 2)
      - Meeting: Banquet: North Carolina State University Chapter, 24 Apr. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 3)
      - Meeting: Chemical Industry Institute of Toxicology, 30 Apr. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 4)
      - Meeting: Press, Lane, 1 May 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 5)
      - Meeting, 16-17 May 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 6)
      - Meeting: Centennial Celebration of University of Minnesota Chapter, 16 May 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 7)
      - Meeting: Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory Energy Advisory Committee, 21-22 May 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 8)
      - Meeting: Annual Banquet: Research Triangle Park Sigma Xi Chapter, 13 Jun. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 9)
      - Meeting: Aspen Institute, 29 Jun. - 3 Jul. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 10)
      - Meeting: Charlotte Chapter of Sigma Xi, 4 Sep. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 11)
      - Meeting: Research Triangle Park Chapter Meeting, 12 Sep. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 12)
      - Meeting: Triangle Area Research Directors Club, 17 Sep. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 13)
      - Meeting: Research Triangle Foundation, 10 Sep. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 14)
      - Meeting: Endless Frontier Conference, 20-21 Sep. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 15)
      - Meeting: Conference Call: Audit Review, 2 Oct. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 16)
      - Meeting: Hungarian Chapter Installation, 22-26 Oct. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 17)
      - Meeting: Carnegie Mellon Public Policy Advisory Board, 10-11 Oct. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 18)
      - Meeting: Triangle Universities Center For Advanced Studies Inc., 11 Nov. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 19)
      - Meeting: Malone Luncheon, 13 Nov. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 20)
      - Meeting: New China Development Corporation, 13 Nov. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 21)
      - Meeting: Diplomat Reception, 20 Nov. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 22)
      - Meeting: Regional Science Association, 14-15 Nov. 1996 (Box 1.062, Folder 23)
      - Meeting: MacArthur Foundation, 12 Dec. 1996 (Box 1.063, Folder 1)
      - Meetings, Dec. 1996 (Box 1.063, Folder 2)
      - Meeting: Duke School of Engineering, 23 Jan. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 3)
      - Meeting: Staff Coordinator, Administration, 4 Feb. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 4)
      - Meeting: Staff Coordination, Programs, 5 Feb. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 5)
      - Meeting: American Association for the Advancement of Science, 13-18 Feb. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 6)
      - Meeting, 24 Feb. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 7)
      - Meeting: Department of Energy, 24-25 Feb. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 8)
      - Meeting: Fornes, Ray, 28 Feb. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 9)
      - Meeting: Annual Meeting: Sigma Xi, 5-9 Mar. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 10)
      - Meeting: Government University Industry Research Roundtable, 12-13 Mar. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 11)
      - Meeting: Vary Coates Seminar, 19-20 Mar. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 12)
      - Meeting: Annual Meeting Debriefing Session, 17 Mar. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 13)
      - Meeting: Laws of Science Seminar, 26 Mar. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 14)
      - Meeting: Anlyan, William, 3 Apr. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 15)
      - Meeting: McGill University Chapter, 17-21 Apr. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 16)
      - Meeting: Banquet: McGill University Chapter, 18 Apr. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 17)
      - Meeting: John Moore's Inauguration, 20-21 Apr. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 18)
      - Meeting: Watson, Bob, 22 Apr. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 19)
      - Meeting: American Association for the Advancement of Science, 23-25 Apr. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 20)
      - Meeting: Covance Dedication, 6 May 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 21)
      - Meeting: Videoconference Town Meeting, 8 May 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 22)
      - Meeting: Long-Range Planning, 12 May 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 23)
      - Meeting: International Union of Pure and Applied Chemistry, 28 May 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 24)
      - Meeting: Visualization Technologies in Environmental Curricula, 12-14 Jun. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 25)
      - Meeting: Fundraising for Annual Meeting, 19-20 Jun. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 26)
      - Meeting: National Coalition for Research and Development, 23-24 Jun. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 27)
      - Meeting: National Coalition for Research and Development, 24 Jun. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 28)
      - Meeting: Price, David, 3 Jul. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 29)
      - Meeting: Aspen Energy Policy Forum, 5-9 Jul. 1997 (Box 1.063, Folder 30)
      - Meeting: Cooperating for Carolina Competitiveness, 11 Jul. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 1)
      - Meeting: International Society for Measurement and Control Grand Opening, 21 Aug. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 2)
      - Meeting: Forum Fundraising, 21-22 Aug. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 3)
      - Meeting: Science Coalition, 11 Sep. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 4)
      - Meeting: Environmental Protection Agency Open House, 30 Sep. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 5)
      - Meeting: Forum Fundraising, 28-29 Sep. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 6)
      - Meeting: Keystone Opportunity Zone, 8 Oct. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 7)
      - Meeting: Conference Call: Audit Review Committee, 10 Oct. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 8)
      - Meeting: Environmental Protection Agency Ground breaking, 20 Oct. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 9)
      - Meeting: Wachovia Bank, 23 Oct. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 10)
      - Meeting: Personnel Law Seminar, 23 Oct. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 11)
      - Meeting: Ehlers, Vern, 27 Oct. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 12)
      - Meeting: Ehlers, Vern, 27-28 Oct. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 13)
      - Meeting: North American Regional Science Association, 6-9 Nov. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 14)
      - Meeting: Environmental Protection Agency Science Advisory Board, 19 Nov. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 15)
      - Meeting: Annual Meeting: Sigma Xi, 18-23 Nov. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 16)
      - Meeting: Duke Chapter, 3 Dec. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 17)
      - Meeting: National Research Council Science and Technology Data Exchange, 15-17 Dec. 1997 (Box 1.064, Folder 18)
      - Meeting: Sandia Labs, National Science Foundation, National Academy of Sciences, 21-22 Jan. 1998 (Box 1.064, Folder 19)
      - Meeting: AmSci Luncheon Speakers, 1998 (Box 1.064, Folder 20)
      - Meeting: International Union of Pure and Applied Chemistry, 29 Jan. 1998 (Box 1.064, Folder 21)
      - Meeting: American Association for the Advancement of Sciences, 12-15 Feb. 1998 (Box 1.064, Folder 22)
      - Meeting: Anderson, Marion, 16 Mar. 1998 (Box 1.064, Folder 23)
      - Meeting: American Nuclear Society, 18 Mar. 1998 (Box 1.064, Folder 24)
      - Meeting: University of North Carolina Conference on Research Integrity, 18-19 May 1998 (Box 1.064, Folder 25)
      - Meeting: Annual Meeting: Sigma Xi, 2-6 Mar. 2000 (Box 1.064, Folder 26)
      - Meeting: Duke University Environmental Law Colloquium, 26-27 Mar. 1998 (Box 1.071, Folder 1)